(Amy:)I'm available
for experimentation.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Not necessary.
(Sheldon:)We know everything
there is to know about kissing.
(Sheldon:)It requires 34 facial muscles
and 112 postural muscles.
(Amy:)Oh, blah, blah, blah.
(Amy:)Give me some sugar, bestie.
(Sheldon:)I'm certainly glad
no one said they were curious
(Sheldon:)about Aztec human sacrifice.
(Penny:)Hey, I know--
let's take Sheldon dancing.
Ooh, I totally want
to see Sheldon dance.
(Bernadette:)I bet he looks like
a spider on a hot plate.
(Sheldon:)No, thank you,
but for the record,
(Sheldon:)I'm an excellent dancer.
(Sheldon:)Proficient in the rumba,
waltz and cha-cha.
(Amy:)Really?
(Sheldon:)I don't see why
that's surprising.
(Sheldon:)I excel at so many things.
(Sheldon:)You've had my sourdough bread.
(Penny:)Did you take dance lessons?
(Sheldon:)Against my will.
(Sheldon:)In the South,
preadolescent children
(Sheldon:)are forced through
a process called cotillion,